Guide to the Stanford University, Center for East Asian Studies, Student Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records, Accession ARCH-2010-032
  - Sahlin, Erik, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 432)
  - Tow, Edna MA (1997), 1995-1997 (Box 14, Folder 433)
  - Vining, Margaret A., 1995 (Box 14, Folder 434)
  - Kitahama, Kiyoshi BA (1996) (Box 14, Folder 435)
  - Wong, Garrin BA (1996) (Box 14, Folder 436)
  - Bauer, Michael MA (1998), 1996-1998 (Box 14, Folder 437)
  - Colyvas, Jeanette MA (1998), 1996-1998 (Box 14, Folder 438)
  - Foy, Clinton MA (1998), 1996-1998 (Box 15, Folder 439)
  - Hague, Elizabeth, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 440)
  - Harlow, Carole M., 1996 (Box 15, Folder 441)
  - Hellawell III, Alan G., 1996 (Box 15, Folder 442)
  - Holbrook, Adam MA (1998), 1996-1998 (Box 15, Folder 443)
  - Hosley, Sheba MA (1997), 19961997 (Box 15, Folder 444)
  - Hungerford, George MA (1998), 1996-1998 (Box 15, Folder 445)
  - Kosuge, Mari MA (1999), 19961999 (Box 15, Folder 446)
  - Kusaki, Kimiko MA (1997), 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 447)
  - Liang, Shih-chi MA (1997), 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 448)
  - Meegama, Sujatha, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 449)
  - Rama, Robert B., 1996 (Box 15, Folder 450)
  - Ruskola, Teemu, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 451)
  - Skabelund, Aaron, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 452)
  - Solotaroff, Jennifer MA (1998), 1996-1998 (Box 15, Folder 453)
  - Speaks, Tiffany MA (1997), 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 454)
  - Tiereny, Robert MA (1997), 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 455)
  - Vanderbilt, Read MA (1997), 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 456)
  - Williams, Blake MA (1997), 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 457)
  - Chen, Julie BA (1997) (Box 15, Folder 458)
  - Lopez, Sarah BA (1997) (Box 16, Folder 459)
  - Su, Irene BA (1997) (Box 16, Folder 460)
  - Usyak, Jennifer BA (1997) (Box 16, Folder 461)
  - Brookhart, John C. MA (1998), 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 462)
  - Carotenuto, Venetia MA (1999), 1997-1999 (Box 16, Folder 463)
  - Flaxman, Caroline MA (1998), 19971998 (Box 16, Folder 464)
  - Hayashibara, Mariko, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 465)
  - Herman, Elizabeth MA (1999), 1997-1999 (Box 16, Folder 466)
  - Hori, Yuko MA (1999), 1997-1999 (Box 16, Folder 467)
  - Kikunaga, Kunie MA (1998), 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 468)
  - Lavin, James MA (1998), 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 469)
  - Leininger, James, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 470)
  - Lieu, Chang MA (1998), 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 471)
  - Nevin Jr., James P., 1997 (Box 16, Folder 472)
  - Oishi, Kyoko M. MA (1999), 1997-1999 (Box 16, Folder 473)
  - Ouyang, Michael M. MA (1999), 1997-1999 (Box 16, Folder 474)
  - Riekert, Philipp MA (1999), 1997-1999 (Box 16, Folder 475)
  - Shaw, Jill J., 1997 (Box 16, Folder 476)
  - Smith, Sean E. MA (1999), 1997-1999 (Box 16, Folder 477)
  - Benson, Carey BA (1998) (Box 17, Folder 478)
  - Aaslid, Ive E., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 479)
  - Baum, Charles, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 480)
  - Boreger, Thomas MA (1999), 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 481)
  - Collins, Ann, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 482)
  - Evers, Jennifer M. MA (1998) (Box 17, Folder 483)
  - Fan, Haihong MA (1999), 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 484)
  - Hansen, Pete, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 485)
  - Kadowaki, Jinichi, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 486)
  - Kanayama, Maki MA (1999), 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 487)
  - King, Michelle T., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 488)
  - Klinck, Heino, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 489)
  - Matsuda, Tandy K.R., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 490)
  - Panton, Jefferson R. MA (1999), 19981999 (Box 17, Folder 491)
  - Schonberg, Anna M., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 492)
  - Segni, Giovanni, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 493)
  - Siu, Rana A., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 494)
  - Tam, Waikeung MA (1999), 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 495)
  - Taylor, Read S., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 496)
  - Westhafer, Susan, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 497)
  - Yao, James S. MA (2000), 1998-2000 (Box 17, Folder 498)
  - Fan, Mandy BA (1999) (Box 17, Folder 499)
  - Polonsky, Sasha E. BA (1999) (Box 17, Folder 500)
  - Tibbles, Darell BA (1999) (Box 17, Folder 501)
  - Wilson, Jordan E. BA (1999) (Box 17, Folder 502)
  - Barr, Katherine, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 503)
  - Chiao, Jeffrey, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 504)
  - Clark, Frank, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 505)
  - Fromm, Martin, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 506)
  - Groschwitz, John, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 507)
  - Hammer, Wolfgang, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 508)
  - Hsu, Andrea C., 1999 (Box 17, Folder 509)
  - Kawamura, Tadaaki, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 510)
  - Krupar, Shiloh, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 511)
  - Nakamura, Shoko MA (2000), 19992000 (Box 18, Folder 512)
  - Price, Kelly, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 513)
  - Sohmen, Philip, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 514)
  - Xu, Lin, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 515)
  - Browdows, James BA (2000) (Box 18, Folder 516)
  - Chiou, Amy BA (2000) (Box 18, Folder 517)
  - Huddleston, Alexandra BA (2000) (Box 18, Folder 518)
  - Pettus, John BA (2000) (Box 18, Folder 519)
  - Brunette, Rachel, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 520)
  - Estes, Anthony, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 521)
  - Fong, Wing N., 2000 (Box 18, Folder 522)
  - Jin, Jiaqi, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 523)
  - Kosaka, Kotaru, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 524)
  - Mahakian, Russell C., 2000 (Box 18, Folder 525)
  - Mun, Laurie K., 2000 (Box 18, Folder 526)
  - Nicholson, Kathy Ann, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 527)
  - Reiman, Ken, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 528)
  - Schultz, Wendy, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 529)
  - Slayton, Thomas, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 530)
  - Snow, Hilary K., 2000 (Box 18, Folder 531)
  - Stansberry, Brian, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 532)
  - Jackson, Andrea BA (2001) (Box 18, Folder 533)
  - Callahan Jr., Edward M., 2001 (Box 18, Folder 534)
  - Chan, Stephanie T., 2001 (Box 18, Folder 535)
  - Chen, Katherine, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 536)
  - Chen, Yin-Ching, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 537)
  - Chia, Wui H.E., 2001 (Box 18, Folder 538)
  - Kushida, Kenji E., 2001 (Box 18, Folder 539)
  - Lin, Terry, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 540)
  - Mencin, Omar G., 2001 (Box 18, Folder 541)
  - Thorpe, Landon P., 2001 (Box 18, Folder 542)
  - Tong, Gianna, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 543)
  - Whiteman, Stephen H., 2001 (Box 18, Folder 544)
  - Yeomans, Belinda, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 545)
  - Chen, Anselm BA (2002) (Box 18, Folder 546)
  - Garratt, Simon BA (2002) (Box 18, Folder 547)
  - Ham, Sarah Mundy BA (2002) (Box 18, Folder 548)
  - Perlmutter, Harry BA (2002) (Box 19, Folder 549)
  - Bolle, Tricia, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 550)
  - Bowler, Kerry, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 551)
  - Bryant, Madika M., 2002 (Box 19, Folder 552)
  - Cho, Han, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 553)
  - Fong, Andrew, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 554)
  - Hwang, Vicky, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 555)
  - Hyun, Yule, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 556)
  - Kim, Eun J., 2002 (Box 19, Folder 557)
  - Kwon, Jung H., 2002 (Box 19, Folder 558)
  - Lee, Jeffrey, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 559)
  - Russell, Frances, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 560)
  - Shin, Suh-Yong, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 561)
  - Sisk, Thomas, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 562)
  - Wolfla, Kevin, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 563)
  - Wong, Grace, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 564)
  - Lee, Eunice BA (2003) (Box 19, Folder 565)
  - Schuerenberg, Elena BA (2003) (Box 19, Folder 566)
  - Tsai, Robin BA (2003) (Box 19, Folder 567)
  - Aden, Nathaniel, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 568)
  - Barraclough, Katherine, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 569)
  - Herzfeld, Brigitta, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 570)
  - Ii, Suzanne, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 571)
  - Iida, Masafumi, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 572)
  - Kim, Linda, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 573)
  - LiCata, Elizabeth, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 574)
  - MacDonald, Andrew, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 575)
  - Mackle, Daniel, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 576)
  - Park, Cheol, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 577)
  - Patel, Rakhi, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 578)
  - Peck, Sara, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 579)
  - Shao, Lige, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 580)
  - Soo, Debby, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 581)
  - Umegaki, Hiroko, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 582)
  - Vance, Brigid E., 2003 (Box 19, Folder 583)
  - Webb, Paul A., 2003 (Box 19, Folder 584)
  - West, Samuel, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 585)
  - Wong, April M., 2003 (Box 19, Folder 586)
  - Yeh, Irene, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 587)
  - Chen, Christine BA (2004) (Box 19, Folder 588)
  - Kawasumi, Jen H. BA (2004) (Box 19, Folder 589)
  - Liu, Tim BA (2004) (Box 19, Folder 590)
  - Loh, Karen BA (2004) (Box 19, Folder 591)
  - Stryjewski, Elizabeth BA (2004) (Box 20, Folder 592)
  - Chang, Cheng David, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 593)
  - Chen, Peijin, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 594)
  - Doody, James, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 595)
  - Gibson, Julie, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 596)
  - Hong, Joon S., 2004 (Box 20, Folder 597)
  - Hsung, Jenwa, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 598)
  - Ip Lau, Suk Yee R., 2004 (Box 20, Folder 599)
  - Ito, Ren, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 600)
  - Liu, Xiao, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 601)
  - Miles, Kevin, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 602)
  - Ng, Hui M., 2004 (Box 20, Folder 603)
  - Nicholson, Virginia S., 2004 (Box 20, Folder 604)
  - Okoye, Chieze, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 605)
  - Quek, Francis H.C., 2004 (Box 20, Folder 606)
  - Richards, Gene, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 607)
  - Shin, Young Y., 2004 (Box 20, Folder 608)
  - Teague, Patrick, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 609)
  - Volz, Michael, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 610)
  - Watabe, Shiho, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 611)
  - Yan, Jiejun, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 612)
  - Huerte, Erica BA (2005) (Box 20, Folder 613)
  - Lee, Mi Young BA (2005) (Box 20, Folder 614)
  - Mastro, Oriana BA (2005) (Box 20, Folder 615)
  - Perlin, Ross BA (2005) (Box 20, Folder 616)
  - Phail-Liff, Adam BA (2005) (Box 20, Folder 617)
  - Rozelle, Whalen BA (2005) (Box 20, Folder 618)
  - Chen, Minqian, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 619)
  - Criddle, Reed, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 620)
  - Fujinuma, Koichi, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 621)
  - Hwang, Amy C., 2005 (Box 20, Folder 622)
  - Kim, Daisy, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 623)
  - Kinney, Christina, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 624)
  - Lee, Helen, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 625)
  - Cho, Hyun-Young BA (2006) (Box 20, Folder 626)
  - Koch, Gabriele BA (2006) (Box 20, Folder 627)
  - Tseng, Chin-Yin BA (2006) (Box 20, Folder 628)
  - Cha, Stephanie BA (2007) (Box 20, Folder 629)
  - Chagzoetsang, Yangchen BA (2007) (Box 20, Folder 630)
  - Hart, William T. BA (2007) (Box 20, Folder 631)
  - Ho, Eileen BA (2007) (Box 20, Folder 632)
  - Jin, Jenny BA (2007) (Box 20, Folder 633)
  - Kuo, Kevin BA (2007) (Box 20, Folder 634)
  - Tanner, Wynn BA (2007) (Box 20, Folder 635)
  - Tollerud, Suzanne BA (2007) (Box 20, Folder 636)
  - Vejo, Maria C. BA (2007) (Box 20, Folder 637)
  - Wood, William Z. BA (2007) (Box 20, Folder 638)